<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GoogleCTF Beginner&#39;s Quest 2019 on shiny-labs</title>
    <link>https://shiny-labs.re/series/googlectf-beginners-quest-2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GoogleCTF Beginner&#39;s Quest 2019 on shiny-labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>shiny-labs@kylma.fr (shiny-labs)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>shiny-labs@kylma.fr (shiny-labs)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 15:18:44 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shiny-labs.re/series/googlectf-beginners-quest-2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GoogleCTF Beginner&#39;s Quest 2019 - Drive to the Target</title>
      <link>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190814-googlectf-beginners-drive-to-the-target/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 15:18:44 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>shiny-labs@kylma.fr (shiny-labs)</author>
      <guid>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190814-googlectf-beginners-drive-to-the-target/</guid>
      <description>Description  Excellent work! With your fine sleuthing skills, you managed to find a picture of the handsome creature with its pet biped. At last friends and companionship may be near!
Like all inhabitants of this world, you spend an inordinate amount of time on the site, stalking and comparing your life to that of others. The first thought that springs to your mind is &amp;ldquo;Why haven&amp;rsquo;t I ever been to Mauritius on holiday?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoogleCTF Beginner&#39;s Quest 2019 - Stop GAN</title>
      <link>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190813-googlectf-beginners-stop-gan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 16:34:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>shiny-labs@kylma.fr (shiny-labs)</author>
      <guid>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190813-googlectf-beginners-stop-gan/</guid>
      <description>Description  Success, you&amp;rsquo;ve gotten the picture of your lost love, not knowing that pictures and the things you take pictures of are generally two separate things, you think you&amp;rsquo;ve rescue them and their brethren by downloading them all to your ships hard drive. They&amp;rsquo;re still being eaten, but this is a fact that has escaped you entirely. Your thoughts swiftly shift to revenge. It&amp;rsquo;s important now to stop this program from destroying these &amp;ldquo;Cauliflowers&amp;rdquo; as they&amp;rsquo;re referred to, ever again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoogleCTF Beginner&#39;s Quest 2019 - Government Agriculture Network</title>
      <link>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190806-googlectf-beginners-government-agriculture-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 15:28:01 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>shiny-labs@kylma.fr (shiny-labs)</author>
      <guid>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190806-googlectf-beginners-government-agriculture-network/</guid>
      <description>Description  Well it seems someone can&amp;rsquo;t keep their work life and their home life separate. You vaguely recall on your home planet, posters put up everywhere that said &amp;ldquo;Loose Zips sink large commercial properties with a responsibility to the shareholders.&amp;rdquo; You wonder if there is a similar concept here.
Using the credentials to access this so-called Agricultural network, you realize that SarahH was just hired as a vendor or contract worker and given access that was equivalent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoogleCTF Beginner&#39;s Quest 2019 - FriendSpaceBookPlusAllAccessRedPremium.com</title>
      <link>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190727-googlectf-beginners-friendspacebookplusallaccessredpremium.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 09:10:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>shiny-labs@kylma.fr (shiny-labs)</author>
      <guid>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190727-googlectf-beginners-friendspacebookplusallaccessredpremium.com/</guid>
      <description>Description  Having snooped around like the expert spy you were never trained to be, you found something that takes your interest: &amp;ldquo;Cookie/www.FriendSpaceBookPlusAllAccessRedPremium.com&amp;rdquo; But unbeknownst to you, it was only the 700nm Wavelength herring rather than a delicious cookie that you could have found. It looks exactly like a credential for another system. You find yourself in search of a friendly book to read. Having already spent some time trying to find a way to gain more intelligence&amp;hellip; and learn about those fluffy creatures, you (several)-momentarily divert your attention here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoogleCTF Beginner&#39;s Quest 2019 - Work Computer</title>
      <link>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190724-googlectf-beginners-work-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 21:12:06 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>shiny-labs@kylma.fr (shiny-labs)</author>
      <guid>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190724-googlectf-beginners-work-computer/</guid>
      <description>Description  With the confidence of conviction and decision making skills that made you a contender for Xenon&amp;rsquo;s Universal takeover council, now disbanded, you forge ahead to the work computer. This machine announces itself to you, surprisingly with a detailed description of all its hardware and peripherals. Your first thought is &amp;ldquo;Why does the display stand need to announce its price? And exactly how much does 999 dollars convert to in Xenonivian Bucklets?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoogleCTF Beginner&#39;s Quest 2019 - Home Computer</title>
      <link>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190724-googlectf-beginners-home-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 11:53:22 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>shiny-labs@kylma.fr (shiny-labs)</author>
      <guid>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190724-googlectf-beginners-home-computer/</guid>
      <description>Description  Blunderbussing your way through the decision making process, you figure that one is as good as the other and that further research into the importance of Work Life balance is of little interest to you. You&amp;rsquo;re the decider after all. You confidently use the credentials to access the &amp;ldquo;Home Computer.&amp;rdquo; Something called &amp;ldquo;desktop&amp;rdquo; presents itself, displaying a fascinating round and bumpy creature (much like yourself) labeled &amp;ldquo;cauliflower 4 work - GAN post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoogleCTF Beginner&#39;s Quest 2019 - Satellite // Introduction to Reversing Go Binaries</title>
      <link>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190722-googlectf-beginners-satellite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 10:03:43 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>shiny-labs@kylma.fr (shiny-labs)</author>
      <guid>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190722-googlectf-beginners-satellite/</guid>
      <description>I picked the binary of the challenge satellite from Google CTF beginner&amp;rsquo;s quest 2019 as a first target to learn go reversing.
Description  Placing your ship in range of the Osmiums, you begin to receive signals. Hoping that you are not detected, because it&amp;rsquo;s too late now, you figure that it may be worth finding out what these signals mean and what information might be &amp;ldquo;borrowed&amp;rdquo; from them. Can you hear me Captain Tim?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoogleCTF Beginner&#39;s Quest 2019 - Ad</title>
      <link>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190720-googlectf-beginners-2019-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 11:56:22 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>shiny-labs@kylma.fr (shiny-labs)</author>
      <guid>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190720-googlectf-beginners-2019-ad/</guid>
      <description>Description of the challenge:  We interrupt this program for a commercial break
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QzFuwljOj8Y
 Solving A flag is hidden in the youtube video:
Flag: CTF{9e796ca74932912c216a1cd00c25c84fae00e139}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoogleCTF Beginner&#39;s Quest 2019 - Enter Space-Time Coordinates</title>
      <link>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190719-googlectf-beginners-2019-enter-space-time-coordinates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 23:53:22 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>shiny-labs@kylma.fr (shiny-labs)</author>
      <guid>https://shiny-labs.re/posts/190719-googlectf-beginners-2019-enter-space-time-coordinates/</guid>
      <description>Description  Ok well done. The console is on. It&amp;rsquo;s asking for coordinates. Beating heavily on the console yields little results, but the only time anything changes on your display is when you put in numbers.. So what numbers are you going to go for? You see the starship&amp;rsquo;s logs, but is there a manual? Or should you just keep beating the console?
 Solving Here we go!
$ file 00c2a73eec8abb4afb9c3ef3a161b64b451446910535bfc0cc81c2b04aa132ed 00c2a73eec8abb4afb9c3ef3a161b64b451446910535bfc0cc81c2b04aa132ed: Zip archive data, at least v2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>